instantdomainsearch.com 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you visit our site and use our products and services. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites (collectively, "Services") offered by Hartshorne Software, Inc. ("us", "we", "our", "Instant Domain Search" or "Hartshorne Software"), or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies.

 **If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time at[help@instantdomainsearch.com](mailto:help@instantdomainsearch.com).**

## Summary

Our web servers automatically log your IP address and information about your web browser. This helps us find people who abuse the service. We retain this information for 30 days. We use Google Analytics and Google Optimize to see how you use the site. Google sets cookies automatically when you visit our website. When you leave our web site by clicking on a link, we include a unique ID provided by Google Analytics. That lets us track whether certain devices, for example, make a purchase our partner web sites. All this seems pretty reasonable to us. Please email [help@instantdomainsearch.com](mailto:help@instantdomainsearch.com) to let us know what we could do better.

## Information We Collect

  *  **Cookies:** As you browse Hartshorne Software’s website, cookies will be automatically placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Google Analytics and Google Optimize ([Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)) will place a cookie on your computer to see how you use the site over time. Our affiliate partner, Conversant, LLC. ([Privacy Policy](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy/)), will use cookies to track purchases made when you click on any link or press enter or return and make a purchase at one of our partners.

  *  **Log information:** When you access our Services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information in aggregate to help understand what types of devices use the Service, and to help detect abuse of the Service. We retain this information for 30 days.

  *  **User communications:** When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We offer some of our services in connection with other websites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Hartshorne Software in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

  *  **Other sites:** This Privacy Policy applies to Hartshorne Software and Hartshorne Software’s other Services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as links from our Services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

## How we Use collected Information

Hartshorne Software only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or any specific notices given for specific Services. Such purposes include:

  * Providing Services to our users;
  * Research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and
  * Developing new services.

If you provide us with personal information when you sign up to our Services and we use that information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

Hartshorne Software processes personal information on servers in Canada, the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own Services.

## Your Choices

Our Services may allow you to opt-out of certain information gathering and sharing or to opt-out of certain Services or features. You will be explained how to do so at each occasion where you have such choices.

## Information Sharing

We may share your information with third parties we use to perform certain functions, such as hosting. These parties will be contractually bound to treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any other confidentiality and security measures instructed by us. Otherwise, we will only share your information if we have your consent, or, we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Hartshorne Software, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Hartshorne Software becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Accessing, updating, and deleting personal information

When you use Hartshorne Software’s Services, we will make efforts to provide you with reasonable access to your personal information, so that such data can be either updated or deleted at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed processing such requests. We may decline to process unreasonable requests, requests which require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. Please contact us at [help@instantdomainsearch.com](mailto:help@instantdomainsearch.com) if you would like access to whatever information we are able to associate with you, or if you would like us to delete any information we are able to associate with you.

Where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, unless if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

## More Information

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time at [help@instantdomainsearch.com](mailto:help@instantdomainsearch.com).
